<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MobApp</string>
    <string name="essteling" translatable="false">Essteling</string>

    <string name="fairytale_title">The wolf and the 3 little pigs</string>
    <string name="fairytale_page_0">Mother pig told her little piglets Peter, Patty and Penny to build a house of their own. The first piglet Peter wants to be ready quickly and builds his house with some straw. So he can start playing quickly.</string>
    <string name="fairytale_page_1">The second piglet, Patty, makes his house out of wood. Patty thought it was fine and prefers to play with his brother.</string>
    <string name="fairytale_page_2">The third piglet, Penny, is the smartest and makes his house solid of stone. At the end of the day, Penny has finished building his house. Just in time for the big bad wolf! All three little pigs quickly flee into their own house. When the wolf is at the houses, he is the first to go to the first house.</string>
    <string name="fairytale_page_3">The house fell over! Fortunately, the piglet just managed to escape and ran into his brother Patty\'s house. The wolf also tries to blow this house down.</string>
    <string name="fairytale_page_4">With a strong wind, the wolf also completely blows this house over! Horrified, Peter and Patty run to their brother Penny to hide from the bad wolf. With all the strength that the wolf has, he also tries to blow this house down.</string>
    <string name="fairytale_page_5">No matter how hard he coughs and sneezes, the house remains firm. The wolf was angry.</string>
    <string name="fairytale_page_6">Peter and Patty were very shocked after today and had decided to make a sturdy new house together with their smart brother. This may take longer, but because of this they were never bothered by the wolf again and they lived happily ever after.</string>
    <string name="volgende_stap">Next step</string>
    <string name="start_fairy_popup">Are you sure you want to start this fairy tale?</string>
    <string name="quit_fairy_popup">Are you sure you want to quit the fairy tale?</string>
    <string name="blaas">Blow in the meter</string>
    <string name="percentage">%1$d %%</string>

    <string name="step">Step %1$d / %2$d</string>
    <string name="in_use">Someone else is using this tale</string>
    <string name="press_button">Press button to start</string>


    <string name="wolf_name">The wulf and the three pigs</string>
    <string name="wolf_location">At point 3 on map</string>
    <string name="wolf_time">3 minutes</string>
    <string name="wolf_desc">Experience the tale of the three little pigs as the wolf</string>

    <string name="placeholder_time">3 minutes</string>
    <string name="placeholder_location">A nice spot</string>

    <string name="hans_name">Hansel and Gretel</string>
    <string name="hans_desc">Experience the tale of Hansel and Gretel</string>

    <string name="cinderella_name">Cinderella</string>
    <string name="cinderella_desc">Experience the tale of Cinderella</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>


</resources>